Women spend a lot of money and a lot of time trying to find the perfect tools for their hair.
What you want to look for when you look for a brush is the diameter of the brush.
For somebody with long hair, this diameter is going to get more tangled.
Once you go through and try to brush your hair out, it's going to get stuck within the masses of hair for your length.
What you can use is a brush like this for in long hair is for the ends, which would be your finishing look.
You can roll your ends in order to achieve that rolling end rounding the face, or you can use in order to get more of that flip.
Somebody with long hair who's looking for a straighter look, we go for a large diameter brush.
The larger the diameter of the brush, the larger the section that you can take.
If you can grab the hair with the brush, then you can blow it out.
This section can grab half of her hair, no matter the length, in one thing.
It's working with less time on you and less energy.
Another great straightening tool is the flat brush, which many people don't appreciate.
If you grab this section of hair, you can clip it together and pull down.
It gives you that straight iron effect and smoothness without having to use such intense heat that the straight iron has.